You’re a jerk, Thom.
Look C
...you have your robotics, and I
j
Why don’t you just admit that
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hyo
I’m not freaked out by- it’s...
...alright! Fine!
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hI
that I’m being chased...
...by
\h\h\h\h"Fourty years later"
Whatever, Thom. We’re done.
R
This is pretty freaky.
Shouldn’t you be down there?
I
It’s not my fault, you know.
Are you ready?
Of co
How’s it looking, Barley?
We
Well that’s perfect.
We’re on in one! All systems go!
Yeah you, go!
Go! Move your asses! Go go go!
I love it! Come on, go!
That’s nice.
Nothing to worry about.
Thom.
There she is.
Now.
You love her.
She is your passion!
Be tender to her.
Be honest! Eh- be tender.
Remind her what love is.
...and, action!
Memory overwrite in progress!
You’re a jerk, Thom!
Ohp- Sorry! Sorry.
Look Celia.
We have to follow our passions.
You have your robotics...
...an
Okay
Speed it up, Thom!
Vivacissimo!
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hWh
freaked out by my robot hand?
Listen Celia, I was young...
...and a dick.
But that’s no reason to
\h\h\hdestroy the world.
Why does he do this?
We already tried that one!
Abort!
Cut!
Whoaaa!
Nooooo!
You broke my heart.
I know.
You forgot me on earth.
I should just crush you.
I’m-
I’m sorry.
Good ad-lib.
Not my fault!
This time.
Quiet on set!
We’re out of time!
Come on!
RAAAAAAAAH!
Memory overwrite, 90%.
Captain! We have to abort!
The world’s changed, Celia...
...maybe we can too.
Memory overwrite complete!
You know.
There
Could’a gone worse.